We're going to talk about the 50 reasons
why you should be using TypeScript.
Reason number one, I'm just kidding.
So for the, you know, I know some of you
when we're talking about TypeScript,
a lot of you probably heard a lot of, well,
talks about the many reasons why TypeScript should be used.
However, for me personally, I've always
wanted TypeScript to be well, a little bit.
I always thought a little bit scary to get into,
because when people talked about it,
they were talking about all in migration
to that kind of stuff.
So when I designed this workshop,
I really designed for people who really
have been curious to use TypeScript with view for a long time.
And especially with view too, that wasn't as easily,
like it was kind of hard to do that,
because it felt like you were doing hacks a lot of the time.
So then people were fighting with TypeScript,
and ultimately wasn't a great experience.
On the other hand, on the other spectrum, when it comes to who
this workshop is for, we have people who've been
itching to use TypeScript, right?
And so they want to learn the fundamentals of how they work together.
And everyone else in between this,
this is who the workshop is designed for.
To get you all really a flavor of what view with TypeScript is
liked, but the key thing to understand, though,
is that this is not a workshop that's designed to make you an expert
in TypeScript.
There are plenty of other wonderful resources on the Friend
and Master's workshop platform.
So if you want to get a really deep dive into TypeScript,
be sure to check those out.
But we'll really be focusing on integrations
and getting people up to speed.
So even if you don't know any TypeScript,
that is totally fine.
You'll be just at home here.
OK, so once again, it's kind of reiterate.
For TypeScript has taken the front end ecosystem by storm.
But again, from my perspective, a lot of times when
we have these popular tools, people do that whole like,
when you're holding in hammer, everything looks like a nail.
So everyone's to put TypeScript in everything.
There are issues with that.
And so I remember just listening to all these talks and thinking,
well, some things kind of not right.
Like, is it really as wonderful as it is,
given that people would talk about all these theoretical benefits
they would get.
And then at the end of the day, they were fighting all these,
whether it's type, type inferences, all that fun stuff.
And so the whole premise of my workshop for me
was what we could just use TypeScript without going all in on it.
How can we progressively move towards it,
use what works well without feeling like it's like the gospel
for all code bases?
And so the key thing to remember as we go through the rest of this,
workshop is that your code is not inferior
because you don't use TypeScript.
I feel like sometimes a lot of times it is spoken in that way
that if you're not using TypeScript somehow,
you're like behind the curve.
And at the end of the day, we have to remember that
TypeScript, like a lot of other tools and texts,
they come with trade-offs and the key thing is whether or not
it's solving problems for you and your team.
If you're a junior team, have perfect tests and everything's working,
and there's no reason to move to TypeScript,
you shouldn't feel pressure too.
So I think that's just a key thing to remember as we talk about this.